신부 들러리
드레스는 구했어?
So, Bernadette, how goes
the hunt for bridesmaid dresses?
원뿔형 도로표지처럼
보이고 싶다면 성공이야
Well, if you don't mind
looking like
an orange traffic cone, great.
나한테 해결책이 있어
AMY: Girlfriends,
I have the answer
to our dress problems.
정말?
BERNADETTE:
Really?
12년 전 내 사촌 아이린이
AMY: 12 years ago,
my cousin Irene
and her entire family died
결혼식 전날 밤에
in a horrific
carbon monoxide accident
일산화탄소 사고로 죽었어
the night before her wedding.
끔찍하다
That's horrible.
그렇지만은 않아
Yes and no.
신부 들러리들이
입을 드레스가
All those bridesmaids dresses
remain unused
아직 남아있고 공짜야
and available to us for free.
유독가스 속에
한 줄기 희망이 있었어
So it seems
that cloud of
odorless deadly gas
had a silver lining after all.
이것 봐
Check it out,
아직 포장되어 있어
still in the bags.
신부 들러리 말고
드레스를 말한 거야
The gowns, not the bridesmaids.
괜찮을지 모르겠다
I don't know.
돌아가신 분들의 드레스잖아
Dead people's dresses?
캡 소매도 좀 그렇다
Yeah, and
cap sleeve
Eh...
눈치채지 않았으면 했는데
Oh, I was hoping
you wouldn't notice.
아이린은 싼 옷이라면
사족을 못 썼어
Irene was always
a slave to a good bargain
when it came to clothes,
난방기도 저렴해서 문제였지
and sadly as it turned out,
space heaters.
아가씨들
Ladies, please.
이곳은 한때
지적 공간으로 활용되었어
These four walls once housed
an intellectual salon
정신적 영양도 공급되고
where the mind
received nourishment
배도 채워졌지
as well as the stomach.
누구의 탓이라 하지 않겠지만,
페니
But through no one's fault,
Penny,
식사 때 나누는
대화의 수준이 떨어졌어
the quality of
dinner conversation
in this apartment
has declined.
다시 말하지만
누구의 잘못이라 할 수 없어
And again, I'm looking at
no one in particular, Penny.
알았어
Fine.
그럼 어떤 얘기를 할까?
What would you like
to talk about, Sheldon?
쉘든한테 그런 질문을?
"What would you like
to talk about, Sheldon?"
우리가 그렇게 싫어?
Why do you hate us?
대화 주제를 준비해왔어
I've prepared a number of topics
초보자부터 고급까지
모두가 좋아할 거야
that should appeal
to both the advanced
and novice
conversationalists.
이번에는 날 쳐다봤잖아
Okay, that time
you looked at me.
당연하지
Who didn't?
피부가 설화 석고처럼 곱잖아
Your skin is
like alabaster.
모공이라는 건 들어봤니?
Do you even
have pores?
첫 번째 주제야
SHELDON:
Topic one:
유럽입자물리연구소에서
빛보다 빠른 입자 발견
"Faster-than-light particles
at CERN--
패러다임을 바꾸는 혁명적 발견인가
"paradigm-shifting discovery
스위스 치즈 구멍처럼
허점 투성인가?
or another Swiss export as
full of holes as their cheese?"
대화 시작!
And converse.
우리 집 가서 웨딩 잡지 볼 사람?
PENNY:
All right, who wants to go
to my apartment and look at
bridal magazines?
Oh, me.
누구의 잘못도 아니지만,
먼저 나가볼게
Through no one's fault, Sheldon,
we're leaving.
같이 가자
Wait for moi.
너도 가려고?
You're leaving?
쉘든, 나도 여자야
Sheldon, sometimes you forget,
I'm a lady.
에스트로겐이 분비되면
광택지를 넘겨야할 욕구를 느껴
And with that comes
an estrogen-fueled need
to page through
그리고 내 몸에 자괴감이 들겠지
thick glossy magazines
that make me hate my body.
새로운 주제다
New topic: women.
여자들은 신비로운 존재인가,
아니면 정신이 나간 걸까?
Delightfully mysterious
or bat-crap crazy?
맞아
Totally.
캡 소매가 어때서?
What's wrong with cap sleeves?
어울리기만 하면 귀엽던데
If you have the right figure
for it, they're adorable.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x08
The Isolation Permutation
Original Air Date on November 3, 2011
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
에이미, 우리 구역에는
어쩐 일이야?
Hey, Amy, what brings you
to our neck of the woods?
너네 신경학과에서
프리온 단백질을 빌려줬어
Your neurology department
loaned me a culture of prions
소해면상뇌증에 관한
연구를 하고 있거든
for my research on bovine
spongiform encephalopathy.
광우병을 빌리려 들렸구나
She popped by to borrow
a cup of mad cow disease.
퇴행성 뇌질환으로
웃기기는 어려운데
It's hard to make degenerative
brain maladies hilarious,
넌 역시 달라
and yet somehow you do it.
식탁에 올려놓으니 기분이 좋네
That's fun to have
in a lunchroom.
실험용 쥐를 고를 때
훨씬 재밌어져
The real fun starts
when you get to pick the rat
말똥말똥한 눈으로
날 물은 놈한테 복수할 기회야
you're going to feed it to,
and maybe you choose
the beady-eyed little mother
who's been biting you all week.
먹고 있는데 좀 그렇다
Please, we're eating.
바닥에 놓고 주제 좀 바꿔볼까?
Can we get that
off the table
and change the subject?
그럴까?
Can we?
기대해
Stand back...
단순 대화가 아닌 대박이야
while I turn this conversation
into a "conver-sensation."
이번에는 너 때문이야
This time, it's your fault.
100가지 주제를
알파벳 순으로 정리했어
I have 100
alphabetized topics from
'Aㅏ티초크는 거대한 엉겅퀴이다'부터
"artichoke-- come on, people,
it's just a giant thistle,"
'수면의 시 zzz'까지 있어
to "zzz-- the onamona-poetry
of sleep."
에이미, 광우병으로
죽으려면 얼마나 걸릴까?
Amy, how long
would it take
for that mad cow disease
to kill me?
4~5년 정도?
I don't know,
four or five years.
안 되겠네
No, it's not gonna do it.
베르나데트가 계속
문자를 보내네
Oy. Bernadette keeps
texting me pictures
페니가 들러리 드레스
입어보고 있나봐
of Penny in bridesmaid dresses.
지금 쇼핑 중이야?
They're out shopping right now?
응
Yeah.
둘이서?
Just the two of them?
그런가봐
I guess.
괜찮아
That's cool, that's cool.
왜 나한테 물어보는 거야?
Why are they asking me
about this stuff?
하트형 네크라인이
뭔지 남자가 어떻게 알아
What guy knows
what a sweetheart neckline is?
(video game music
playing over TV)
레너드, 이제 결승선이 보인다
Leonard's coming down
the home stretch!
이랴!
Come on, horsey,
you can do this!
대퇴근육아, 조금만 힘내라
Damn. Come on, thigh muscles,
you can do this!
(panting)
이겼다!
Yes! First place.
키가 더 작았다면
훌륭한 기수였을텐데
I would have been a great jockey
if I weren't too tall.
말이 무서워서 문제지
And scared of horses.
쉘든, 이리와
Sheldon, you're up.
뭐?
What?
네 차례라고
Come on, it's your turn.
신선한 공기 좀 마시자 했잖아
We said we'd get more fresh air.
미안
Sorry.
집중을 못 하겠어
I'm a little distracted.
에이미랑 연락이 안돼
I can't seem
to get in touch with Amy.
이메일, 화상채팅
I tried e-mail, video chat,
트위터도 해봤고
tweeting her,
posting on
페이스북, 문자 다 안돼
her Facebook wall,
texting her, nothing.
전화는 해봤어?
Did you try calling her
on the telephone?
전화라
The telephone.
넌 참 단순하지만
You know, Leonard,
in your own simple way,
그게 제일 현명할 때가 있어
you may be the wisest of us all.
음성 메시지
Voice mail.
알 수가 없네
Curiouser and curiouser.
걱정이 되면 직접 가보자
If you're worried,
we can go over there
and see if she's all right.
그래
Okay.
그쪽 동네에 살쾡이가
출현했다고 들었는데
You know, I heard
in the news
a bobcat has been spotted
in her neighborhood.
에이미가 살쾡이한테
먹히지는 않았을 거야
I don't think
Amy was eaten by a bobcat.
에이미가 살쾡이한테
먹혔다고 누가 그래?
Who thinks Amy was
eaten by a bobcat?
네가?
You do?
난 그냥 흥미로운
뉴스를 말해준 거였어
Leonard, I was just mentioning
an interesting local news item.
너 때문에 에이미가
잡아먹힌 건지 걱정되잖아
Now, thanks to you, I'm worried
Amy's been eaten by a bobcat.
살쾡이는 그냥 잊어
Forget about the bobcat.
네가 계속
상기시키고 있잖아
How can I?
You won't stop talking about it!
♪ Everybody hurts ♪
♪ Sometimes ♪
(voice breaking):
♪ Everybody cries ♪
(sobbing)
♪ Everybody hurts ♪
Sometimes.
슬퍼하고 있어
She sounds weepy.
슬픈 건 싫어,
가자
I don't like weepy. Let's go.
Uh...
친구잖아
She's your friend.
좀 도와줘
Step up.
에이미
Amy. Amy. Amy.
안녕
Bye.
어디 가는데?
Where are you going?
난 솔로니까 빠질게
I'm single, I don't
need this crap.
쉘든, 여기는 어떻게 왔어?
Sheldon, what are you
doing here?
모든 연락수단에
반응이 없었잖아
You didn't respond to
any of my electronic
communications.
혼자 있고 싶었어
I wanted to be alone.
무슨 일인지
얘기 좀 들어줄까?
Would you like to talk about it?
싫다고 해도
받아들일 수 있어
And keep in mind that "no"
is a perfectly viable answer.
쉘든, 내 멘탈이
붕괴되고 있어
Sheldon, my world is
crumbling around me.
순서를 지키자
Point of order.
네가 괴로워하고 있으니
As you're in distress,
it would be customary
난 따뜻한 음료부터 권해야 해
for me to offer you
a hot beverage.
하지만 내가 손님이잖아
But I'm a guest in your home,
네가 음료를 내오는 게 맞지
so it would be customary for you
to offer me a beverage.
음료 문제는
어떻게 해결하면 좋을까?
How do you want to proceed
vis-a-vis beverages?
상관없어
It doesn't matter.
모든 게 상관없어
Nothing matters.
분위기 전환을 해보자면
If you'd like to take your mind
off what's troubling you,
주변에 살쾡이가
출현했다고 들었어
uh, word on the street is
a bobcat has been spotted.
페니와 베르나데트가
날 빼고 쇼핑갔어
Penny and Bernadette
went shopping
for bridesmaids dresses
without me.
그래서 슬퍼하는 건가?
And that made
you feel... sad?
응
Yes.
그럴 줄 알았어
I knew it.
계속해
Just keep going.
난 잘할 수 있어
I guess I'm
good at this.
나랑 지내는 걸
좋아하는 줄 알았는데
It's just, I thought
they liked hanging out with me,
착각하고 있었나봐
but I guess I was
fooling myself.
걔들이 놀러왔을 때
When they were
over here,
음료를 내오지 않은 적 있어?
did you fail to offer
them a beverage?
그걸로 앙금이
남을 수도 있거든
'Cause I can see how that
could stick in someone's craw.
쉘든, 질문할게 있어
Sheldon, I'm going
to ask you something,
열린 마음으로
들어주면 좋겠어
and I'd like you
to keep an open mind.
물론이지
Always.
지금 이 순간에
At this moment, I find myself
인간적 친밀함과
신체 접촉을 갈망하고 있어
craving human intimacy
and physical contact.
Oh, boy.
우리는 정신적 관계를
맺고 있잖아
You know ours is a
relationship of the mind.
제안할게
Proposal.
하룻밤만 격렬한 사랑을 나누자
One wild night
of torrid lovemaking
내 영혼을 달래고
허리가 뒤틀리도록
that soothes my soul
and inflames my loins.
대안이 있어
Counterproposal.
네 머리를 쓰다듬으면서
I will gently
stroke your head
'에이미 착하지'를 반복할게
and repeat, "Aw,
who's a good Amy""
이러면 어때?
How about this?
프렌치 키스로
7분 동안의 천국 맛보기
French kissing--
seven minutes in heaven
2루까지만 가자
culminating in second base.
목 마사지
Neck massage...
그런 다음에
마실 것 좀 부탁할게
...then you get me
that beverage.
껴안자,
협상 끝!
We cuddle. Final offer.
알았어
Very well.
Oh, boy.
2루도 근처에 있어
I'm just saying,
second base is right there.
특이하게 꾸미고 싶어
Mm, I'm thinking
about adopting
파이프나 외알 안경이나
some quirky affectation,
like a pipe or a monocle
팔자 수염도 좋아
or a handlebar mustache.
인도인 모노폴리 아저씨를
원하는 여자들을 위해?
For all those girls out there
looking for
the Indian Monopoly man?
이곳은 안전하지 않아
This is not a safe place.
무슨 말을 못하겠네
You can't share anything here.
너네 둘은 여자 관리 좀 잘해
The two of you need to get
your women in line!
뭐?
What?
어젯밤에 하프를 들으면서
달래줘야 했다고
Last night I was strong-armed
into an evening
of harp music and spooning
에이미가 감정적으로 변했어
with an emotional
Amy Farrah Fowler.
내가 계획했던 밤이 아냐
This on a night
that I had originally
designated for solving
중력보다 스핀이 클 때의
시공간 기하학 연구하고
the space-time geometry
in higher-spin gravity
레고 데스스타를
만드려고 했어
and building my Lego Death Star.
왜냐고?
너네 여자친구 때문이야
And why? Your gal pals,
Penny and Bernadette,
에이미를 빼고
웨딩 쇼핑인지 뭔지를 갔거든
went out shopping for some
wedding nonsense without Amy,
배려심이라고는 전혀
볼 수 없는 행동이지
an action they took
with no thought or regard
내 시간을 방해하고,
끈이론의 미래를 망치고
as to how it would affect me,
the future of string theory
레고도 못 만들었어
or my Lego fun time!
그래서 어쩌라고?
What do you want us
to do about it?
내 요지를 파악하지 못 했네
You clearly weren't listening
to my topic sentence:
여자들 관리 좀 하라고
Get your women in line!
에이미한테 사과하고
제대로 돌려놔
You make them apologize to Amy
and set things right.
나는 곰인형이 아니라
과학자라고
I am a man of science,
not someone's snuggle bunny!
내가 왜 페니랑 얘기해야 돼?
Why do I have
to talk to Penny?
내 여자친구도 아니잖아
She's not my girlfriend.
4년 전에 점심 초대했잖아
You invited her to lunch
four years ago.
페니와 관련된 모든 것은
너로부터 시작되었어
Everything about her is on you;
you make it so!
- 돼지고기는 페니꺼
- 고마워
- Moo-shu is Penny.
- Thank you.
쉘든은?
Where's Sheldon?
어젯밤 늦게까지 못 잤대
He was up late last night,
저녁을 일찍 주고 재웠어
so I gave him an early dinner
and put him to bed.
정말 다정하다
That's so sweet.
새벽에 깨면
놀아달라고 하겠지
Yeah, but now he's gonna be
up at dawn and want to play.
So, listen, guys,
쉘든이 어제 늦게 잔 이유는
the reason he was up late
is because he was
에이미를 달래고 있었대
taking care of Amy.
속상한 일이 있나봐
She's kind of upset.
왜?
Why?
너네 둘만 쇼핑하러 가서
상처 받은 것 같아
Her feelings got hurt
because you guys
went dress shopping without her.
그럴 거라고 했잖아
I told you that
would happen.
에이미가 들러리를
한 적이 없어서
Okay, look, this is her first
time being a bridesmaid
너무 흥분하고 있어
and she's just getting
a little crazy with it.
다른 문화권의
들러리에 대해 알려주는데
She keeps on telling us
stories about bridesmaid
traditions in other cultures,
and they're all about
옷 벗고
서로 씻겨주는 내용이야
getting naked and
washing each other.
그리고 생리 주기를
서로 맞추라 하고 있어
Yeah, and
she keeps trying
to figure out if our
cycles have synced up
우리를 자궁 자매라
부르고 싶대
so we can call ourselves
"The Three Menstra-Teers""
한번 정도는
우리끼리 가도 될 것 같았지
We thought it would be easier to look
at dresses one time without her.
후회된다
I feel terrible.
나도 그래
I know. Me, too.
We'll talk to her.
잠깐
Hey, wait,
에이미가 어떻게 알았지?
how did she find out?
라지가 말했어
Raj did it.
같은 상황이 오면
또 그럴 거래
And he says he
would do it again.
미안해
Hey, I'm sorry.
네가 사진을 보내서
별 생각 없이 그랬어
You sent me the picture;
I wasn't thinking.
평소에는 입이 무겁잖아
- Oh, Howie.
- Well, hey, I'm usually
pretty good at
not blabbing.
얘네에 대해 말한 건
떠벌린 적이 없어
You tell me
tons of stuff
about these guys,
and I never repeat it.
무슨 얘기 했는데?
- What do you tell him?
- Oh,
별 얘기 아냐
you know, just pillow talk.
걱정할 거 없어
You guys have nothing
to worry about.
우리가 사귈 적에
너도 무슨 얘기했어?
Hold on, did you talk about us
when we were dating?
네 소소한 비밀은
잘 지키고 있어
No. All your little
secrets are fine.
철저하게 지켜졌지
Yes, absolutely fine.
이따 말해줄게
(giggles):
I'll tell you later.
나와라, 종양
Come on, tumor.
악성 교모세포종이 필요하단다
Come on, tumor, Mama needs an
aggressive little glioblastoma.
앗싸, 종양이다!
Yay, brain tumor!
네가 소식을 들었을 때와는
다른 반응이겠지
Probably not the same reaction
you had when you got the news.
- Hi.
- Hello.
무슨 일이야?
What are you doing here?
그날 같이 안 가서
사과하고 싶었어
Well, look, we just
wanted to apologize
for not bringing you
with us the other day.
그럴 필요 없어
That's not necessary--
it's like Sesame Street says:
이런 속담도 있잖아
"One of these things
is not like the other,
모난 돌이 정 맞는다고
one of these things
should die alone."
에이미, 우리에게 기회를 줘
Come on, Amy, let us
make it up to you.
여자들끼리의 시간을 갖자
We'll have a girl's night;
네가 하고 싶은대로 하자
we'll do whatever
you want.
네가 추천한
한국 목욕탕에 가서
We can go down
to the Korean baths
항상 말하던 것도 해보자
and do that thing
you were talking about
서로 씻기는 것 말야
where we wash each other.
손 말고
떼밀이 수건으로
With-with loofah mitts,
no hands.
괜찮아,
언젠가는 이렇게 됐겠지
It's okay.
I'm glad this happened.
이제 현실을 깨달았어
I can stop pretending
that some beautiful girl
예쁘고 귀여운 두 분이
나랑 있고 싶지는 않겠지
and her cute-in-
the-right-light friend
want to hang out with me.
에이미, 정말 미안해
Amy, we're really sorry.
그래, 우리가 잘못했어
Yeah, we
feel awful.
너네가 처음도 아닌데 뭘
Don't. I'll be okay.
You're not the first girls
친구로 지내다가
왕따 당한 적 많아
I thought were friends with me
who ended up shunning me.
초등학교, 중학교
It's like elementary school,
junior high,
고등학교, 대학교, 대학원
high school, undergrad,
grad school,
그리고 노르웨이에
한 학기 있을 때도 그랬지
and that semester abroad
in Norway all over again.
에이미, 이러지 마
Oh, come on, Amy.
넌 이해를 못하고 있어
You don't get it.
이 뇌를 봐봐
Look at this brain.
그러고 싶지 않아
I don't really want to.
이게 우리야
This is us.
베르나데트는 분석적이고
과학적인 좌뇌야
Bernadette,
you are the analytical,
scientific left hemisphere.
페니는 창의적이고
즉흥적인 우뇌지
Penny, you're the creative,
spontaneous right hemisphere.
그럼 에이미는?
And where's Amy?
이 작은 종양이지
She's right here--
the sad little tumor
같이 쇼핑하러 갈 사람도 없어
no one wants to go
dress shopping with.
에이미, 넌 종양이 아냐
Amy, you're not a tumor.
페니,
종양이 아니라고 말해줘
Penny, tell her
she's not a tumor.
(retching)
(phone ringing)
알렉산더 그라함 벨이
전화를 발명했을 때
Did you know that when
Alexander Graham Bell
invented the telephone,
이렇게 받으라고 제안했어
he proposed answering
it with "ahoy"?
Ahoy.
괜찮다
I like it.
에이미? 너야?
Amy? Is that you?
술 마셨어?
Have you been drinking?
존나 많이 마셨다고?
I'm sorry, I bet my sweet what?
알았어, 곧 갈게
Well, all right.
We're on our way.
무슨 일이야?
What's going on?
주류 판매점
주차장에서 취해있대
It would seem Amy is drunk
in a liquor store parking lot.
정말?
에이미가?
Really? Amy?
넌 여자가 없어서 다행이야
Leonard, be glad
you can't keep a woman.
골치 아프네
They are a handful.
이게 누구야
Oh, look.
쉘든이랑 꼬맹이네
It's Sheldon and little Leonard.
꼬맹아, 안녕
Hi, little Leonard.
안녕, 에이미
Hi, Amy.
안녕, 곰돌이
Hey, Cuddles.
곰돌이?
Cuddles?
그래, 곰인형처럼 껴안았다
Yes, Cuddles.
We cuddled.
철 좀 들어라
Grow up, Leonard.
에이미, 여기서 뭐하는 거야?
- Amy, what are you doing here?
- Well,
와인 한 병 사러 왔지
I came here to get
a bottle of wine
슬플 때 마시라고
페니한테 배웠거든
like Penny taught me to do
when you're sad.
그런데 왜 계속 여기 있어?
Yeah, but why didn't you
go back to your apartment?
고등학교 안 다녔어?
Didn't you go
to high school, Leonard?
인기 많은 애들은
주차장에서 놀잖아
Parking lots are where
all the cool kids hang out.
그 자식들이
날 초대한 적도 없지만
Not that the rat bastards
ever invited me.
집에 데려다 줄게
Maybe we should
get you home.
잠깐, 쉘든
Oh, hang on, hang on,
hang on. Sheldon,
가게에 들어가서
what would it take for you
to go into that liquor store,
맥주 한 병을 산 다음에
buy a bottle of hooch,
건너편 모텔로
나를 데리고 가서
take me across the
street to that motel,
날 맘대로 다뤄주게 하려면
어떤 방법이 있을까?
and have your way with me?
그래, 어떻게 하면 될까?
Yeah, Sheldon,
what would it take?
부탁인데 제발 가자
I'm begging both of you,
please, let's go.
Okay.
Come on.
- Upsy-daisy.
- Whee!
드디어 2루를 찾았나 보네
Ooh, finally someone
found second base.
네 기분 잘 알아
I know how you feel.
누군가 칼로
전두엽을 쑤시는 것 같아
I got a knife slicing
through my frontal lobe, too.
(knocking)
안녕
Hi.
뭘 원해?
What do you want?
우정 팔찌 돌려줄까?
Do you want me to give
the friendship bracelet back?
그런 거 준 적 없는데
I never gave you
a friendship bracelet.
네가 줬다고 상상하면서
혼자 선물한 적이 있어
When we first met, I made one
and pretended you gave it to me.
원하면 돌려줄게
You can have it back
if you want.
널 위해 만든 거잖아,
계속 가졌으면 좋겠어
No, you made that for you;
I want you to have it.
속상한 거 알고
네 마음 이해해
We know you're upset,
and you have every right to be,
한 번만 기회를 줘
but if it's okay with you,
we'd like a second chance
to make things right.
정말 미안해
PENNY:
We are really sorry,
그리고 우리 마음을
표현할 방법을 생각해봤어
and we were trying to think
of some way to show you
how much we
care about you.
내 부탁을 들어주면
정말 고마울 거야
BERNADETTE:
Which is why
it would mean so much
if you would agree
들러리 반장을 해주면 좋겠어
to be the maid of honor
at my wedding.
지금 장난 치는 거야?
What? Wait, is this some kind
of practical joke?
노르웨이에서 친구라는 것들이
Like in Norway,
when my "friends"
날 사우나에
수달이랑 가둔 것처럼?
trapped me in a sauna
with a horny otter?
들러리 반장을 부탁할게
No. I-I want you to be
the maid of honor.
세상에
Oh, my gosh.
이런 부탁은 처음이야
No one's every asked me to be
the maid of honor before.
아니지
Well, that's not true.
그런 적이 있긴 한데
다들 죽어버렸지
Once, but then they all died.
해주는 거야?
So is that a yes?
응!
(laughs):
Yes. Yes.
Oh, my gosh,
할 일이 너무 많네
I-I have so much to do.
신부파티랑 미혼녀 파티도 있고
There's the bridal shower
and the bachelorette party.
미혼녀 파티는 어떻게 할까?
What should we do for
the bachelorette party? (gasps)
원주민 한증막에 가면 되겠다
Oh, I know-- we'll go to
a Native American sweat lodge,
페요테를 복용하고,
진흙에 뒹굴고
we'll take peyote,
roll around in the mud,
베르나데트의 몸에
풍요신의 상징을 칠하자
and paint fertility symbols
on Bernadette's naked body.
그러면 되겠네
So that's happening.
그러자
Yeah, sure, sure.
베가스도 재밌는데
Vegas is fun, too.
눈물 날 것 같아
I feel like crying.
호르몬 때문일 수도 있고
Of course, I could
just be hormonal.
아니면 생리 주기가 같아졌나?
Oh, wait. Maybe our menses are
finally syncing up. Bernadette?
베르나데트?
페니?
No? Penny?
- 미안
- 정말?
- Sorry.
- Really?
그래, 맞아
Okay, yeah.
Yay!
들러리 반장 에이미의
결혼식 전 영상입니다
Maid of honor
Amy Farrah Fowler's
amazing behind-the-scenes
wedding video,
시작!
take one.
그냥 드레스 입어보는 건데
We're just trying on dresses--
이런 것도 녹화해야 돼?
do we really need
to record this?
네가 반장이니?
I'm sorry, are you
the maid of honor?
난 신부야
I am the bride.
다시 가자, 액션!
So no. And action.
어때?
What do you think?
좋아!
I love it!
수녀였어?
AMY:
What are you, a nun?
살 좀 보자고
Come on, bestie,
let's see some skin.
에이미, 정말 섹시하네
BERNADETTE:
Amy! Looking sexy!
저 안에 거울 있거든
You think they don't
have mirrors in there?
나도 내가 어떤지 알아
I know how I look.
Oh...!
베르나데트, 완전 예뻐
Bernadette, you
look beautiful!
- 맞아
- 고마워
AMY: You do.
- Thank you.
페니만큼은 아니지만 예뻐
Not Penny beautiful,
but beautiful.
페니, 네 차례야
AMY: Come on, bestie,
you're up.
잠시만
PENNY:
Give me a minute.
왜 이렇게 오래 걸려?
What is taking
you so long?
에이미, 어딜 쳐들어와
Oh, Amy!
Get the hell out of here!
미안
Sorry, sorry.
(groans): Oh, God.
- Amy!
- Sorry.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==